

Fakrul Islam Fahim

Graphics Designer

🙎 14/2, Tikkapara, Mdpur, Dhaka-1207

+8801820008521

M fakrulfahim786@gmail.com

in LinkedIn

Objective Overview

I am excited about the opportunity to secure a **Graphics Designer** position, where I can apply the expertise and insights I've gained throughout my 4+ years of professional experience. My aim is to create designs that enrich user experiences and drive business success.

Key Skills:

- Creative Design
- Image Editing
- Poster Design
- logo design

- E-Commerce DesignVideo editing
- Social Media Poster Design

- Motion Graphics
- UI/UX Design (Basic)

Tools:

- Photoshop
- Illustrator
- **rc** Lightroom
- Pr Premiere Pro (Basic)

- Filmora
- **Figma**

Portfolio:







<u>Portfolio</u>

Experience:

Sep 2021 to Current

Graphics Designer at Mediusware Ltd

Dhaka - Bangladesh

Technical Stack: Creative Design, Image Editing, Social Media Post

Design, video editing.

May 2021 to Nov 2022 Image Editor at PathLinerLab

Dhaka – Bangladesh (**Remote**)

Technical Stack: Image Editing, Social Media Post Design, Creative

Design,

It's a **Freelance based company** who mostly work for USA clients. We mostly work

with Image Editing.

Oct 2019 to Apr 2021 **Graphics Designer** at <u>bZm Graphics Limited</u>

21 Dhaka – Bangladesh

Technical Stack:Image Editing, Social Media Post Design.

EDUCATION QUALIFICATION:

Diploma In Engineering (Computer)

Name of Institution : F.K. Polytechnic Institute

Board : BTEB

Technology : Computer **Session** : 2019-20

Result : 3.50 Out of CGPA- 4

Secondary School Certificate (SSC)

Name of Institution : Quadria Taiyabia Alia Kamil Madrasha

Board : Madrasha

Group : Arts
Year of passing : 2018

Result : G.P.A -4.35

PERSONAL DETAILS:

Name : Mohammad Fakrul Islam

Father's Name : Md Fozlur Rahman

Mother's Name : Farjana Begum

Date of Birth : 22 March 2000

Religion : Islam

Nationality : Bangladeshi

Marital Status : Unmarried

Permanent Address: Village- Ghorashal, P.O - Ghorashal, P.S- Muradnogor,

District-Cumilla.

LANGUAGE:

BanglaEnglishHindiUrdu

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION:

Self motivated, Hard working, Dynamic, Discipline, Adaptable Stuff, Overall, I organize my work and time very efficiently and effective.

Signature

(Fakrul Islam)